<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>book singing waiter tenors Archives - Singing Waiters Hire UK</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.singingwaitershire.co.uk/tag/book-singing-waiter-tenors/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.singingwaitershire.co.uk/</link>
	<description>Fun and Fantastic Surprise Opera Performances!</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:29:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.singingwaitershire.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/cropped-Hartley_voices_church_Singers-32x32.png</url>
	<title>book singing waiter tenors Archives - Singing Waiters Hire UK</title>
	<link>https://www.singingwaitershire.co.uk/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Russ, tenor</title>
		<link>https://www.singingwaitershire.co.uk/singers/russ-tenor</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[operasingingwaiters]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 13:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Singers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[book singing waiter tenors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tenor singing waiters]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.singingwaitershire.co.uk/?p=91</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Russ, tenor is a stunning opera singer and a outlandishly funny performer with his BMus and MMus at the Guildhall School of Music and Drama in voice on an unconditional place where he studdied with Ian Kennedy. After leaving college Russell has made his mark as a popular tenor performing for events throughout the UK &#8230; <a href="https://www.singingwaitershire.co.uk/singers/russ-tenor" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Russ, tenor"</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.singingwaitershire.co.uk/singers/russ-tenor">Russ, tenor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.singingwaitershire.co.uk/">Singing Waiters Hire UK</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignright wp-image-346 size-medium" src="https://www.singingwaitershire.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Russell-tenor-hire-e1519388187461-243x300.png" alt="Tenor Singing Waiter Russ for hire" width="243" height="300" srcset="https://www.singingwaitershire.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Russell-tenor-hire-e1519388187461-243x300.png 243w, https://www.singingwaitershire.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Russell-tenor-hire-e1519388187461-768x947.png 768w, https://www.singingwaitershire.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Russell-tenor-hire-e1519388187461-831x1024.png 831w, https://www.singingwaitershire.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Russell-tenor-hire-e1519388187461.png 911w" sizes="(max-width: 243px) 85vw, 243px" />Russ, tenor is a stunning opera singer and a outlandishly funny performer with his BMus and MMus at the Guildhall School of Music and Drama in voice on an unconditional place where he studdied with Ian Kennedy. After leaving college Russell has made his mark as a popular tenor performing for events throughout the UK and Europe. His tenor opera credits include Tamino (The Magic Flute), Title role in Albert Herring, Pedrillo (The Abduction from the Seraglio), Don Basillio (The Marriage of Figaro), Don Jose (Carmen), Count Almaviva (The Barber of Seville) Gaston (La Traviata) and the second brother in the world premiere of Laurence Roman’s Isabella and the Pot of Basil at Covent Garden and Buxton. Choral works include Handel’s Messiah, Haydn’s Creation, Nelson Mass &amp; The Seasons, Charpentier’s Messe De Minuit &amp; Te Deum, Gounod’s Messe Solennelle,Haazen’s Missa Luba, Mozart’s Requiem, Vesperae Solennes &amp; Coronation Mass, Rossini’s Petite Messe, Stainer’s Crucifixion,Beethoven’s Choral Symphony, Britten’s St Nicholas, Orff’s Carmina Burana and numerous Bach cantatas and passions singing the role of the Evangelist.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.hartleyvoices.co.uk/live-performances/singing-waiters/"><img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-238 size-medium alignleft" src="https://www.singingwaitershire.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/opera_singing_waiters_hire_18-1-237x300.png" alt="Tenor singing waiter hire" width="237" height="300" srcset="https://www.singingwaitershire.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/opera_singing_waiters_hire_18-1-237x300.png 237w, https://www.singingwaitershire.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/opera_singing_waiters_hire_18-1.png 567w" sizes="(max-width: 237px) 85vw, 237px" /></a>Russell has a very keen interest in the works of Gilbert and Sullivan, going so far as to write his Masters thesis on their life and music. He has performed many of the principal tenor roles across the Savoy opera range including The Defendant, Marco, Frederic, Hilarion, Ralph, Captain Fitzbattleaxe, Richard Dauntless, Earl Tolloller, Duke, Alexis, Nanki-Poo and Box, only three left! Recently Russell has been accepted to sing principal tenor in the world renowned “Grims Dyke Opera Company”. His recital work is also recognized in other fields of English music, most recently song settings of the poetry of Housman in “The Blue Remembered Hills” for the Worcester festival.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignright wp-image-182 size-medium" src="https://www.singingwaitershire.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/opera_singing_waiters_hire_32-213x300.jpg" alt="Opera tenors singing waiters booking" width="213" height="300" srcset="https://www.singingwaitershire.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/opera_singing_waiters_hire_32-213x300.jpg 213w, https://www.singingwaitershire.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/opera_singing_waiters_hire_32.jpg 335w" sizes="(max-width: 213px) 85vw, 213px" />Not only happy in operatic roles, Russell is also a keen concert recitalist and after dinner entertainer, having performed seven times with his Young Proms colleagues in the West Midlands area, and having raised over £100,000 for numerous local and national charities. Further afield Russell also works for the London agency Hartley Voices with its group AKA Opera providing unaccompanied opera classics for after dinner and wedding entertainment.</p>
<p>Russell is also very proud to have a strong group of private students for both vocal and music theory tuition, with many students reaching Grade 8 and even beyond to Diploma level.</p>
<p>When wanting warmer climes, Russell spends most summers performing in the south of France, ranging from full scale operas, to concerts in converted barns.</p>
<p>Russell is also a fellow of the London College of Music (FLCM).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.singingwaitershire.co.uk/singers/russ-tenor">Russ, tenor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.singingwaitershire.co.uk/">Singing Waiters Hire UK</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
